OLUDARE OLUWAJUYITAN

+669 3040 3307 | +234 8100 982062 | Bangkok, Thailand

o_oluwajuyitan@sloan.mit.edu | ddrightnow@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/oludare-oluwajuyitan/

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Preteen years, I liked to build machines, early career, I liked to build systems, now I am at the stage where I like to build companies. I am a data-driven business builder, with an MBA from MIT Sloan/Asia School of Business. I help companies to scale, by focusing on 3 main areas: Project Management. 2) Process design and optimization 3) Business Strategy. I have worked in various industries - real estate (proptech) and ecommerce, across key units -Strategic Planning, Business Intelligence, Operations and BD. These experiences enable me to see things from different points of view, and design effective strategies that drive value for organisations. I am multilingual, with both management expertise and technical skills in data analytics and robotic process automation (RPA). I implement ideas by transforming company visions into executable operational workflows.

EXPERIENCE

SELLORATE Operations & Project Manager

Bangkok, Thailand September 2021 to date

Operations & Project Management:

- Manage multiple projects (Agile Methodology) across different teams from C-suite to operations, marketing, agent, and developer teams.
- Redesigned operational process flows for developer team, driving corporate developer clients growth from 140 to 300+
- Initiated project to consolidate various CRM process flows and onboarding automations, led to an increase from 800+ to 2600+ agents.
- Coach and coordinate tasks across staff in different geographical locations (New York, Hawaii & Hong Kong).
- BI & Data Management:
- Data Strategy: Set guidelines on data collection, data access governance, standardized data usage practices across the company, creating central data sources for the team.
- Data guardian over customer databases. Ensure best practices are employed in the collection and storage of customer data. 0
- Led project for clean-up of company data, standardized CRM data across board, speeding up daily task execution and reducing operational errors.
- Manage and monitor python scripts working on the backend. Request for improvements and fixes from IT support team, as business needs evolve.

ANANDA DEVELOPMENT

Bangkok, Thailand Jul 2019 to August 2021

Operations & Strategy Manager (Digital Platform) Operations & Strategy:

- Grew user base by 80% to 1800 projects (housing over 1.6m people), becoming the leading company in Thailand, by redesigning marketing strategy, operational and sales process and increasing size of the sales funnel.
- Coordinated with various functions and departments including management team, both internal and external teams, to ensure team alignment, company culture was maintained, and project deliverables were met. Presented recommendations to board of directors.
- Initiated project to develop new lead & marketing channels. Created 2 digital marketing channels. Reduced cost of lead generation by 50+%.
- Led Geodatabase project, creating custom maps to manage lead and geo data, reducing duplicity of information obtained from multiple 0 sources. This led to cost savings by the reduction in outbound sales efforts, and an increase in the productivity of on-field sales teams.
- Performance Management: Set & Monitor team and individual KPIs. Interview new hires and outsource staff.
- BI & Data Management:
- 0 Created central data source for company business data, aggregating data from marketing, sales, and customer service teams. Plugged into PowerBI dashboard to enable teams see an interactive breakdown of customer profiles and identify areas for improvement in service delivery.
- Robotic Process Automation: Built RPA Robots & hosted on Amazon Cloud EC2 Instances for 10x increase in task processing speed.
- Data mining & segmentation: Identified geolocation of 14,000 leads (projects housing over 13m people), used non-black box model to organise leads into segments.
- Built reporting PowerBI Dashboards.

ALLIANCE FOR FINANCIAL INCLUSION

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia Jun - Aug 2018

Summer Associate - Data Strategy

- Systems Modelling: Built a systems model of the AFI data portal through several iterations, whilst interacting with different AFI departments. It highlighted 5 key improvement areas for data collection and usage withing AFI.
- Improved Process: Authored publication on data management process workflow "in the context of financial inclusion", highlighting common issues, solutions, and practices of country data champions.
- Stakeholder Management: Formed data management team with 7 government central bankers to delineate constraints of national data management processes. Organiser in a data capacity building event for 30+ central bankers from South America, Africa, and Southeast Asia.

EDUCATION

ASIA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS in collaboration with MIT Sloan Management

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia 2017 - 2019

- · Recipient of ASB Full Fellowship
- AL Consulting Projects:
 - Astro TV, Malaysia Growth Hacking Strategies using User data segmentation for the Astro Go Mobile Application.
 - Ancora Group, Indonesia Digital Transformation Strategy for a cohesive user experience across all channels.
 - Creador, Malaysia Business Development & Market Entry Strategy for portfolio company Bake with Yen.
 - Esquel, Malaysia Machine learning prediction model to predict QA defects in the production line.
 - Ananda Development, Thailand Business Model Development for Mobile Platform Application.

KHARKIV NATIONAL AUTOMOBILE AND HIGHWAY UNIVERSITY

Kharkiv, Ukraine

- BSc, Mechanical Engineering
- Russian Language Diploma

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Speak English (IELTS 8.5/9.0), Yoruba, Fluent Russian (Full working proficiency).
- Software: Asana, UIPath, PowerBI, AWS (Certified Solutions Architect), HubSpot, Activecampaign. Familiar: Tableau, JIRA, Confluence
- Skills: Python, SQL, RPA, GitHub: https://github.com/ddrightnow/Machine-Learning-Projects/tree/master/Highlight%20Projects
- Co-President of International Student Council, NIDO Thailand Financial Secretary
- Hobbies: Football, Aerial Cinematography.